T.C. Rotunda

Walnut Creek, CA 94596 | tcrotunda@gmail.com | (714) 883-7973

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tcrotunda/ | GitHub: https://github.com/tcrotunda

Summary

Data Specialist with 6+ years of experience working as a Business Analyst and Data Analyst for top financial firms such as JP Morgan, BNY Mellon, and Charles Schwab. Self-starter, fast learning, and can retain information at a high level. Motivated to learn new technologies. Have a passion for data, and excel in team-oriented environments. Highly detail-oriented, and able to juggle multiple projects at a time. Excellent written and verbal communication skills. Certificate in Data Analytics and Visualization through University of California, Berkeley.

Technical Skills

Python, JavaScript, Tableau, R, SQL, MongoDB, VBA, Hadoop, Jira, Confluence, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, SAP Business Objects

Employment

Charles Schwab (Apex Systems)

San Francisco, CA

Business Analyst May2020 - Present

- Lead daily project scrum calls to ensure timely competition of user stories and appropriate allocation of resources
- Work with developers to migrate ETF trade order processing file from former vendor to new vendor
- Create documentation for import and export feeds for Aladdin trading system
- Cleanup Dealer/Branch/Issuer data for Aladdin trading system

JPMorgan Chase & Co.

New York, NY

Associate Business Data Analyst

February 2019 - June 2019

February 2016 - January 2019

Business Data Analyst

- Analyzed and managed primary and secondary sourced data for the US Funds Management Data Warehouse (FMDW), specifically
 minimizing data errors for the Finance Team for financial reporting purposes
- Led and assisted with projects to maintain data feeds of sourced data for FMDW, and to streamline/automate/improve new
 downstream data feeds to other business units
- Communicated and coordinated with various lines of business, and serve as a liaison between business and technology to help improve business processes and drive changes to our ETL
- Used SAP Business Objects to query data from FMDW for analysis, reporting (daily, monthly and quarterly), UAT testing, and data quality purposes
- Maintained SAP Business Objects infrastructure and data model/data mapping for FMDW
- Worked with international teams from Europe and Asia

BNY Mellon Boston, MA

Associate Business Analyst

June 2014 - January 2016

- Maintained data and data flow for multiple systems for the Wealth Management Fixed Income trading desk
- Worked directly with vendor for application updates and new features to meet end user needs
- Served as a liaison between Portfolio Managers (users) and the technology group
- Updated and adjusted SQL queries to find specific data for ad hoc or future needs
- Helped manage and mitigate risk within the business unit

EverFi Inc.

Newton, MA

Services and Curriculum Intern

June 2013 - May 2014

Performed Level-2 Technical Support and testing for technology-based education system

Education

University of California, Berkeley

Berkeley, CA

Certificate in Data Analytics

January 2021

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in Excel, VBA, Python, R, JavaScript, SQL Databases, Tableau, Big Data, and Machine Learning.

Suffolk University Sawyer Business School

Boston, MA

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration Management, Information Systems minor

May 2014

Awards: Magna Cum Laude | GPA: 3.77